{
  "title": "Japanese Kanji and Hiragana Reading Quiz",
  "description": "Challenge your knowledge of Japanese Kanji and Hiragana readings with this quiz. Each question presents a Kanji character, and you need to choose the correct Hiragana reading from the options. Test your proficiency in reading Japanese characters and enhance your language skills!",
    "items": [
      {
        "question": "木",
        "answer": "き",
        "options": ["みず", "たいよう", "ひ", "き"]
      },
      {
        "question": "日本",
        "answer": "にほん",
        "options": ["ちゅうごく", "かんこく", "にほん", "タイ"]
      },
      {
        "question": "猫",
        "answer": "ねこ",
        "options": ["いぬ", "さかな", "とり", "ねこ"]
      },
      {
        "question": "学生",
        "answer": "がくせい",
        "options": ["せんせい", "いしゃ", "エンジニア", "がくせい"]
      },
      {
        "question": "雨",
        "answer": "あめ",
        "options": ["ゆき", "さんしょう", "かぜ", "あめ"]
      },
      {
        "question": "花",
        "answer": "はな",
        "options": ["くさ", "き", "ばら", "はな"]
      },
      {
        "question": "食べる",
        "answer": "たべる",
        "options": ["のむ", "ねる", "はしる", "たべる"]
      },
      {
        "question": "車",
        "answer": "くるま",
        "options": ["バス", "じてんしゃ", "でんしゃ", "くるま"]
      },
      {
        "question": "家族",
        "answer": "かぞく",
        "options": ["ともだち", "となり", "しんせき", "かぞく"]
      },
      {
        "question": "夢",
        "answer": "ゆめ",
        "options": ["ひとみ", "あくむ", "ゆめ", "じっけん"]
      }
    ]
  }
  